1. What organization is responsible for the 802.11 wireless networking standards?
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

2. Which of the following is the modern name for the 802.11ac standard?
Tags: Wi-Fi, 802.11

3. Which wireless standard is referred to as Wi-Fi 6?
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

4. What is the primary reason for the introduction of simplified Wi-Fi generation names like Wi-Fi 5 and Wi-Fi 6?
Tags: Wi-Fi

5. Which of the following are valid simplified generation names for Wi-Fi standards? (Select all that apply)
Tags: Wi-Fi

6. Which frequency bands are supported by the Wi-Fi 5 (802.11ac) standard?
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

7. Which Wi-Fi generation introduced support for operation in the 6 GHz band?
Tags: Wi-Fi

8. Select two features introduced with Wi-Fi 6 (802.11ax):
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

9. Which of the following best describes Wi-Fi 4 (802.11n)?
Tags: 802.11

10. Which modulation technique introduced in Wi-Fi 6 allows for higher throughput and more efficient use of spectrum?
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

11. Select three enhancements introduced in Wi-Fi 6 to improve performance in dense environments:
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

12. Which Wi-Fi standard introduced BSS Coloring and what is its primary benefit?
Tags: 802.11, Wi-Fi

13. Which of the following features are supported by Wi-Fi 6 (802.11ax)? (Select all that apply)
Tags: Wi-Fi, 802.11

14. Which wireless frequency range is commonly used by both Wi-Fi and Bluetooth technologies?
Tags: 2.4 GHz

15. Which frequency range allows for the most non-overlapping Wi-Fi channels?
Tags: 6 GHz, channel

16. What is the term used to describe how much spectrum is used for a wireless signal?
Tags: bandwidth

17. What is a 'channel' in the context of wireless networking?
Tags: channel

18. Which of the following are valid wireless bandwidth sizes? (Select all that apply)
Tags: bandwidth

19. Why might the 2.4 GHz band experience more interference than the 5 GHz or 6 GHz bands?
Tags: 2.4 GHz, overlap

20. Select two benefits of using the 5 GHz band over 2.4 GHz:
Tags: 5 GHz, channel, bandwidth

21. Which statement best describes the use of channels in wireless networking?
Tags: channel, overlap

22. What happens when you use a wider bandwidth (e.g., 80 MHz instead of 20 MHz) on a wireless network?
Tags: bandwidth

23. Why are only three 20 MHz channels in the 2.4 GHz band considered non-overlapping in most countries?
Tags: 2.4 GHz, channel, overlap

24. Select three reasons why the 6 GHz band improves wireless performance compared to 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz:
Tags: 6 GHz, bandwidth, channel

25. A technician needs to deploy a high-throughput wireless solution in a crowded apartment building. Which configuration is most likely to minimize interference and maximize speed?
Tags: 6 GHz, bandwidth, spectrum

26. Which of the following bandwidth values are supported in modern 802.11 networks? (Select all that apply)
Tags: bandwidth

27. What is the typical wireless frequency range used by Bluetooth technology?
Tags: Bluetooth, 2.4 GHz

28. Which of the following best describes BluetoothΓÇÖs intended usage scenario?
Tags: Bluetooth, short range, personal devices

29. Approximately what is the maximum consumer range for Bluetooth communication?
Tags: Bluetooth, short range

30. Why is Bluetooth considered an unlicensed wireless technology?
Tags: Bluetooth, ISM band, unlicensed frequency

31. Which of the following are common Bluetooth use cases? (Select all that apply)
Tags: Bluetooth, headsets, wireless audio, personal devices

32. Which of the following statements accurately describes the ISM band used by Bluetooth devices?
Tags: Bluetooth, ISM band, unlicensed frequency

33. Select two key limitations of Bluetooth communication:
Tags: Bluetooth, short range

34. Why is Bluetooth considered more suitable than Wi-Fi for connecting headsets or wearable devices?
Tags: Bluetooth, headsets, personal devices

35. A technician is troubleshooting interference with Bluetooth devices. Which nearby technology is most likely the source of the problem?
Tags: Bluetooth, 2.4 GHz, unlicensed frequency

36. Why is Bluetooth more likely to suffer interference in a crowded office environment compared to other wireless technologies?
Tags: Bluetooth, 2.4 GHz, ISM band, unlicensed frequency

37. Select three valid technical characteristics of Bluetooth operation:
Tags: Bluetooth, 2.4 GHz, short range, ISM band

38. Which scenario would most likely cause Bluetooth connectivity to degrade?
Tags: Bluetooth, 2.4 GHz, interference

39. Which of the following are true about Bluetooth's operating range and use cases? (Select all that apply)
Tags: Bluetooth, short range, headsets, personal devices

40. What does RFID stand for?
Tags: RFID, radio frequency identification

41. Which device is commonly used to scan a passive RFID tag?
Tags: RFID, passive RFID

42. What is the key difference between NFC and traditional RFID?
Tags: NFC, near field communication

43. Which of the following are common uses for RFID technology? (Select all that apply)
Tags: RFID, passive RFID, tags, point-of-sale

44. What kind of communication is used by NFC-enabled payment systems like tap-to-pay?
Tags: NFC, near field communication, point-of-sale, device pairing

45. What is a key difference between passive and active RFID tags?
Tags: RFID, passive RFID, active RFID, tags

46. What kind of wireless communication does NFC extend to enable two-way interaction?
Tags: NFC, RFID, near field communication

47. Select two limitations of NFC communication:
Tags: NFC, short range, near field communication

48. Why are passive RFID tags often used in inventory tracking systems?
Tags: RFID, passive RFID, tags

49. Which of the following best explains why passive RFID is preferred in environments like retail and manufacturing?
Tags: RFID, passive RFID, tags

50. Select three key differences between RFID and NFC technologies:
Tags: RFID, NFC, passive RFID, near field communication

51. In which scenario is active RFID preferred over passive RFID?
Tags: RFID, active RFID

52. Which of the following are characteristics of Near Field Communication (NFC)? (Select all that apply)
Tags: NFC, near field communication, point-of-sale

