1. Question: Which type of USB connector is reversible and supports high-speed data and video transmission?
   Tags: USB-C, connector, data transfer

2. Question: What is the primary use of wired mobile device connectors such as USB and Lightning?
   Tags: charging, data transfer, USB, Lightning

3. Question: Which proprietary wired connector is used primarily on older Apple mobile devices?
   Tags: Lightning, connector

4. Question: Which of the following are common types of wired connectors for mobile devices? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: USB, USB-C, miniUSB, Lightning, connector

5. Question: A user needs a wired connection that supports DisplayPort, HDMI, Thunderbolt, and data transfer. Which connector would best meet all of these requirements?
   Tags: USB-C, connector, data transfer

6. Question: What is one major advantage of the Lightning connector over older USB connectors like miniUSB or microUSB?
   Tags: Lightning, connector

7. Question: Which two older USB connector types were commonly used in early mobile devices? (Select two)
   Tags: microUSB, miniUSB, USB

8. Question: Which features are commonly associated with modern USB-C connectors? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: USB-C, charging, data transfer, connector

9. Question: Which statement accurately describes how USB-C enables support for multiple signal types such as DisplayPort and Thunderbolt?
   Tags: USB-C, connector, data transfer

10. Question: What are some challenges IT professionals face with supporting wired connectors in mixed-device environments? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: USB, USB-C, Lightning, charging, connector

11. Question: What technical feature allows USB-C to provide consistent performance regardless of how the cable is inserted?
   Tags: USB-C, connector

12. Question: Which wireless technology is commonly used to connect a mobile device to wireless headsets and speakers?
   Tags: Bluetooth, wireless, wireless headset, wireless speaker

13. Question: What does NFC (Near Field Communication) typically require in order to operate?
   Tags: NFC, near field communication, wireless

14. Question: Which of the following devices commonly use Bluetooth to communicate wirelessly? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth, wireless, wireless headset, wireless speaker

15. Question: What is one of the main use cases for NFC in a mobile device?
   Tags: NFC, near field communication, wireless

16. Question: Which wireless technology typically requires pairing with a PIN or passcode during setup?
   Tags: Bluetooth, pairing, wireless

17. Question: Which two wireless technologies are commonly built into modern mobile devices for short-range communication? (Select two)
   Tags: Bluetooth, NFC, wireless

18. Question: Which features are typically true of Bluetooth connections? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth, wireless, wireless headset, stylus

19. Question: Which statement best explains why NFC is preferred for secure access and tap-to-pay systems over Bluetooth?
   Tags: NFC, near field communication, wireless

20. Question: Which Bluetooth characteristic allows multiple devices like a stylus, keyboard, and speaker to stay connected simultaneously?
   Tags: Bluetooth, pairing, wireless

21. Question: Which challenges or limitations are commonly associated with Bluetooth technology? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth, wireless, wireless headset

22. Question: What is the key difference between tethering and using a mobile hotspot?
   Tags: tethering, hotspot, internet sharing

23. Question: Which term refers to using a smartphone as an internet router for other devices?
   Tags: hotspot, mobile hotspot, internet sharing

24. Question: Which of the following terms are associated with using a mobile device to share its internet connection? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: tethering, hotspot, PAN, internet sharing

25. Question: Which mobile device feature allows multiple users to connect and share one phoneΓÇÖs internet connection via Wi-Fi?
   Tags: mobile hotspot, hotspot, internet sharing

26. Question: What is one reason a mobile device may not support hotspot or tethering features?
   Tags: hotspot, tethering, internet sharing

27. Question: Which two technologies can be used to implement tethering from a mobile device? (Select two)
   Tags: tethering, internet sharing

28. Question: Which scenarios best describe the use of a Personal Area Network (PAN)? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: PAN, Bluetooth, tethering

29. Question: Which factor most directly impacts performance when multiple users connect to a mobile hotspot?
   Tags: hotspot, internet sharing

30. Question: Why might USB tethering be preferred over Wi-Fi tethering in a corporate troubleshooting scenario?
   Tags: tethering, USB, internet sharing

31. Question: Which of the following are valid limitations of using mobile tethering or hotspot features? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: hotspot, tethering, mobile hotspot, internet sharing

32. Question: What is the primary purpose of using a stylus with a mobile device?
   Tags: stylus, digital pen

33. Question: Which feature often allows a stylus to perform different actions based on how hard you press?
   Tags: stylus, pressure sensitivity

34. Question: Which of the following are common characteristics of modern styluses? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: stylus, Bluetooth stylus, pressure sensitivity

35. Question: Why is device compatibility important when selecting a stylus for a tablet?
   Tags: stylus, digital pen, compatibility

36. Question: What type of device allows stylus-based input on a desktop or laptop computer?
   Tags: drawing pad, digitizer, stylus

37. Question: Which two functions are commonly associated with modern styluses? (Select two)
   Tags: stylus, digital pen, pressure sensitivity

38. Question: Which scenarios best demonstrate effective stylus usage? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: stylus, drawing pad, pressure sensitivity

39. Question: Why might a Bluetooth stylus not function properly on a tablet, even if both devices support Bluetooth?
   Tags: stylus, Bluetooth stylus, compatibility

40. Question: What makes drawing pads a preferred tool for digital artists using desktops or laptops?
   Tags: drawing pad, digitizer, pressure sensitivity

41. Question: Which technical limitations can affect the performance of a stylus or drawing pad? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: stylus, drawing pad, Bluetooth stylus, digitizer

42. Question: What is the main benefit of using a headset with a built-in microphone?
   Tags: headset, microphone

43. Question: Which connector type is typically used for analog headsets with microphone support?
   Tags: TRRS, audio jack, wired headset

44. Question: Which of the following are types of headset connections used with mobile devices? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: wired headset, wireless headset, TRRS, Bluetooth headset

45. Question: Which of the following describes a key tradeoff when using a wireless Bluetooth headset instead of a wired headset?
   Tags: Bluetooth headset, wireless headset

46. Question: What is the primary purpose of the additional 'ring' in a TRRS audio connector?
   Tags: TRRS, microphone, audio jack

47. Question: Which two connector types support both audio and microphone signals on mobile headsets? (Select two)
   Tags: TRRS, Bluetooth headset, microphone

48. Question: Which features are commonly found in modern wireless headsets? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: wireless headset, Bluetooth headset, microphone

49. Question: Which issue might occur if a TRRS headset is plugged into a TRS-only audio jack?
   Tags: TRRS, audio jack, microphone

50. Question: Why might a USB headset be chosen over a TRRS analog headset in a modern computing environment?
   Tags: USB, wired headset, microphone

51. Question: Which technical factors may affect the performance or compatibility of headsets across devices? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth headset, TRRS, USB, compatibility

52. Question: Why might someone use a portable Bluetooth speaker with their mobile phone?
   Tags: Bluetooth speaker, audio output, portable speaker

53. Question: How does a wireless speaker typically connect to a mobile phone?
   Tags: wireless speaker, Bluetooth speaker

54. Question: Which of the following are characteristics of portable wireless speakers? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: portable speaker, Bluetooth speaker, audio output

55. Question: What typically happens to audio playback when a Bluetooth speaker is connected to a smartphone?
   Tags: audio output, Bluetooth speaker, wireless speaker

56. Question: Why might a portable speaker suddenly stop playing audio while in use?
   Tags: portable speaker, Bluetooth speaker

57. Question: Which two connection types are commonly used to output audio from a mobile device? (Select two)
   Tags: audio output, Bluetooth speaker, TRRS

58. Question: Which functions are typically managed automatically when a Bluetooth speaker connects to a smartphone? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth speaker, wireless speaker, audio output

59. Question: Which issue is most likely to cause intermittent audio playback from a Bluetooth speaker connected to a mobile phone?
   Tags: Bluetooth speaker, wireless speaker, audio output

60. Question: Why might a phone fail to redirect audio to an external Bluetooth speaker even though it shows as connected?
   Tags: Bluetooth speaker, audio output, compatibility

61. Question: Which technical limitations might affect the performance or compatibility of portable wireless speakers? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: Bluetooth speaker, wireless speaker, audio output, compatibility

62. Question: What is the primary function of a built-in webcam on a mobile device or laptop?
   Tags: webcam, built-in camera, camera

63. Question: Which port type is most commonly used to connect external webcams to computers?
   Tags: USB camera, external camera

64. Question: Which of the following devices typically include a built-in camera? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: webcam, built-in camera, camera

65. Question: Which application is most commonly associated with the use of webcams on laptops?
   Tags: webcam, video conferencing, built-in camera

66. Question: What is one reason a user might choose an external USB webcam over a built-in one?
   Tags: external camera, USB camera, webcam

67. Question: Which two features are typical of external USB webcams? (Select two)
   Tags: USB camera, external camera

68. Question: Which tasks typically involve the use of a webcam? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: webcam, camera, video conferencing

69. Question: Why might a USB webcam fail to work on a desktop even though it's physically connected?
   Tags: USB camera, external camera, webcam

70. Question: A user connects an external USB webcam to a laptop, but it is not recognized by their video conferencing app. What is the most likely solution?
   Tags: USB camera, external camera, video conferencing

71. Question: Which of the following factors could limit the use of a webcam for video conferencing? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: webcam, camera, USB camera

72. Question: What is the main purpose of a docking station when used with a laptop?
   Tags: docking station, laptop dock, interface expansion

73. Question: Which device provides additional ports and is commonly connected to a laptop via USB?
   Tags: port replicator, USB hub

74. Question: Which features are typically provided by a docking station? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: docking station, interface expansion

75. Question: What is one advantage of using a docking station with a laptop in a workplace setting?
   Tags: docking station, laptop dock, interface expansion

76. Question: How does a port replicator differ from a full docking station?
   Tags: port replicator, USB hub, interface expansion

77. Question: Which two components are commonly connected through a docking station? (Select two)
   Tags: docking station, interface expansion

78. Question: Which scenarios would benefit from using a port replicator? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: port replicator, USB hub, laptop dock

79. Question: Why might a high-performance docking station use proprietary connectors instead of standard USB-C?
   Tags: docking station, laptop dock, interface expansion

80. Question: A user connects a USB-based port replicator but cannot use dual external monitors. What is the most likely reason?
   Tags: port replicator, USB hub, interface expansion

81. Question: Which of the following limitations are commonly associated with USB-based port replicators? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: port replicator, USB hub, interface expansion

82. Question: Which of the following is a common function you can perform using a trackpad on a laptop?
   Tags: trackpad, gesture

83. Question: What is one reason a user might disable the trackpad on a laptop?
   Tags: trackpad, disable

84. Question: Which of the following are input devices commonly found on laptops? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: input device, trackpad, touchscreen, microphone

85. Question: A user complains that their laptop trackpad no longer responds to two-finger scrolling. What is the most likely cause?
   Tags: gesture, multitouch, trackpad

86. Question: Select two reasons why a technician might replace a built-in laptop pointing device with an external one.
   Tags: trackpad, external input, pointing device

87. Question: Which of the following input devices may be integrated into modern laptops? (Select all that apply)
   Tags: trackpad, touchpad, input device, stylus

88. Question: Which physical principle is most commonly used in modern laptop touchpads to detect finger movement?
   Tags: trackpad, capacitive, input technology

89. Question: What component or layer is responsible for interpreting raw touchpad input into gestures like pinch-zoom or swipe?
   Tags: gesture, driver, trackpad

90. Question: Select two reasons why capacitive trackpads generally outperform resistive input surfaces in laptops.
   Tags: capacitive, multitouch, trackpad

